CODY LAWSON UI/UX DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Email

cody@codylawsonux.com

Website

codylawsonux.com

SOCIAL

dribbble.com/_cody

instagram.com/codylawson

twitter.com/_codylawson

SKILLS

HTML (v5)

CSS (v3, SCSS, Stylus)

Javascript (ES2017, ReactJS, Angular)

Design (Sketch 3, Illustrator, Balsamiq)

Data Visualization (D3, Highcharts)

Prototyping (Invision, Marvel)

HELLO!

My name is Cody Lawson, I'm a User Interface Developer with over five years of experience. I did a short internship with Esri in 2012 and began working there fulltime in 2013 developing GIS web applications for companies like Walmart, Guy Carpenter, Metlife, and government agencies like the National Geospatial Agency and the Department of Energy.

EXPERIENCE

2013-Present Esri

User Experience Developer

At Esri I worked closely with our customers to translate their complicated business practices into easy to use, workflow-driven web applications. I Designed applications from the requirements gathering stage, through wireframe and prototyping, and eventually implemented my designs

on the front-end.

2012 Summer Esri

Internship: User Experience Developer

Designed and implemented internal websites for Esri as well as design the UX and look and feel of Community

Maps, an Esri product released in 2013.

2010-2013 We3

Freelance Web Developer

Founded in partnership with two other students, we designed and implemented websites for a yoga studio, a marketing agency in Redlands, and developed a brand

guideline for a law office in San Diego.

EDUCATION

2009-2013

B.S. Web Design and Interactive Media

Art Institute of California

REFERENCES

Available upon request